http://azchildren.org/privacy

Events
Need Help?
Blog
Print
|
Children’s Action Alliance (CAA) appreciates the interest that you have taken in our organization. As a donor and user of our Site, we want to provide you with an understanding of how we use information and maintain the privacy of our donors and users. We respect the importance that donors and users of our Site place on the security of their personal information. As such, CAA will not trade, share or sell a donor’s personal information with anyone else, nor send donor mailings on behalf of other organizations. We have established this policy to educate donors and users about how we acquire and utilize user information. This privacy policy also serves as notice that by visiting this Site or donating online or through USPS, you as the user, consent to the practices described in this Privacy Policy.
This Privacy Policy applies online at AZchildren.org and through donations received through USPS (and each sub-domain associated with this URL) which we refer to as the Site. While the Site may contain links to other sites that are operated by third parties, this Privacy Policy does not apply to the other sites, whether those sites are somehow affiliated with CAA. For information related to the Privacy Policy of any other sites, please find and read the privacy policies on the pages associated with those other sites. This Privacy Policy also does not apply to practices, persons, or entities that CAA does not exercise control over, employ, or manage.
CAA generally collects two types of information: Personal Information and Aggregate Information. Personal Information includes any information voluntarily provided to the Site by the user, which may include: name, email address, mailing address, phone, occupation, credit card, debit card, personal preferences, and/or other account-related information. Personal Information does not include Public Personal Information. Public Personal Information is information which the user discloses publicly through message boards, home pages, linked pages, forums, discussions, sponsorships, public activity, social networks, blogs, or the like. Because of the public nature of certain activity, which is voluntarily entered by the user, CAA cannot exercise the same control and provide confidentiality for Public Personal Information. Furthermore, engagement in public activity is voluntary and as such, the user’s implicit consent is understood.
Aggregate Information includes non-personally identifiable information about a user, such as most frequently accessed webpages, date/time of webpage viewing, time spent on webpages, number of visits to webpages, type of browser, type of computer, cookie preferences, type of web service, IP address and/or search terms entered.
CAA automatically collects Aggregate Information as a user accesses the Site. We obtain this information in a collective manner, meaning no single person can be identified through the collection, storage, or use of Aggregate Information. We may use the Aggregate Information internally for demographic tracking, internal market research, research, education, dissemination, creation of personalized content, trouble shooting, server diagnostics, Site administration, trend analysis, movement analysis (within the Site), and/or general information purposes. We may also share Aggregate Information with research grant recipients, content providers, sponsors, service providers, and/or other third parties. The Site may employ various tools such as cookies, web beacons, or packaged commercial products (e.g. Google Analytics) to collect the Aggregate Information.
The user possesses ultimate control over the information the user provides CAA. For example, Personal Information is divulged voluntarily by the user; therefore, the user may decide whether to provide the information. Also, users may opt out of receiving various informational communications from CAA. Users may also set their browsers to refuse cookies and other information collection tools; however, certain areas of the Site may not function at full capacity without these tools enabled.
Enter keyword(s), do NOT press enter, search results will show below.
More results...
